<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <title>Anya Danilova Archive</title>
  <subtitle>Archive of thoughts, things, process</subtitle>
  <link href="https://anyadanilova.com/archive/feed.atom" rel="self" />
  <link href="https://anyadanilova.com/archive/" />
  <updated>2025-10-14T00:00:00Z</updated>
  <id>https://anyadanilova.com/archive/</id>
  <author>
    <name>Anya Danilova</name>
    <email>hello@anyadanilova.com</email>
    <uri>https://anyadanilova.com/</uri>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <title>RSS and stuff</title>
    <link href="https://anyadanilova.com/archive/posts/2025-10/2025-10-14/" />
    <updated>2025-10-14T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>https://anyadanilova.com/archive/posts/2025-10/2025-10-14/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I really don&#39;t know why, but I feel that all of this is right. Instagram brings clients (as some people say) and anxiety. I don&#39;t expect this blog to bring me any of that. This should be a safe space for posting momentary work stuff, but sometimes smartass texts as well. I really like the RSS idea that was suggested to me by this amazing person I met in a train with a faulty AC in 30 degrees (so...maybe that was a dream?), and I would like to thank my friend &lt;a href=&quot;https://ya.codes/&quot;&gt;Aleksandr&lt;/a&gt; for helping me with setting it up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I checked, not a lot of people use RSS, so it&#39;s a perfect ratio of sh*tposting and visibility. If you follow me this way, you must have really &lt;s&gt;weird&lt;/s&gt; serious reasons to do so. And thank you for that, truly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And few pictures to mark this week&#39;s work, otherwise I feel like I haven&#39;t done anything.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;https://anyadanilova.com/archive/posts/2025-10/img/3-10.png&quot; alt=&quot;Alt text 3&quot; loading=&quot;lazy&quot;&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;The only way I know how to test Armenian is still through downloading a hunspell dictionary and put it in Indesign 🫠&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;https://anyadanilova.com/archive/posts/2025-10/img/4-10.png&quot; alt=&quot;Alt text 4&quot; loading=&quot;lazy&quot;&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;Ok, I feel bad for letting my aggression go off like this, but hear me out, if I scream at chatGPT, doesn&#39;t it mean that I scream into the void?..&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;https://anyadanilova.com/archive/posts/2025-10/img/5-10.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Alt text 5&quot; loading=&quot;lazy&quot;&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;The microscope testing, so far this is the best option I&#39;ve got for taking with me to France and document punches. More on that later&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>October. Me, Myself and AI</title>
    <link href="https://anyadanilova.com/archive/posts/2025-10/2025-10-07/" />
    <updated>2025-10-07T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>https://anyadanilova.com/archive/posts/2025-10/2025-10-07/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;In August I asked ChatGPT for a life advice. One of the life advices was to create a blog for myself but open if people want to see. What could go wrong, what can be simpler, right?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, after two months of me being pseudo-developer and screaming and uppercasing at ChatGPT,behold. This is a blog that I made on the basis of 11ty, without no particular need or reason. But it is out there now. I&#39;ll try to post pictures and stories that happened during the month, so I could trick myself into thinking that I actually do something valuable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So that people could leave this blog/archive faster, I put my experimental sans(not an official name) in the works. In parallel, I work on it and persuade myself that it also makes sense.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;https://anyadanilova.com/archive/posts/2025-10/img/1-10.png&quot; alt=&quot;Alt text for img 01&quot; loading=&quot;lazy&quot;&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;Hey, funky!&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now that I think I made it all work -ish, I&#39;m going to write more about how much fun I had with Rezak Armenian (that&#39;s sarcasm, I don&#39;t understand how I&#39;ll publish it) and how simple it was to create a website and a blog on GitHub Pages (that&#39;s sarcasm, but hey, I only spent around a month of my time on this and 20 bucks on ChatGPT, I guess I don&#39;t need people anymore!)&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>September start</title>
    <link href="https://anyadanilova.com/archive/posts/2025-09/2025-09-15/" />
    <updated>2025-09-15T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>https://anyadanilova.com/archive/posts/2025-09/2025-09-15/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Originally I was supposed to start in August, but oh well. Here&#39;s my highlights of September as I remember them. Working on my website with ChatGPT was fun, Rezak Armenian Extrabold is a disaster, Rezak Armenian Black is a fun disaster, script for Rezak Black Incised always gives me weird good pics.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;https://anyadanilova.com/archive/posts/2025-09/img/1.png&quot; alt=&quot;Alt 1&quot; loading=&quot;lazy&quot;&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;Working on my website&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;https://anyadanilova.com/archive/posts/2025-09/img/2.png&quot; alt=&quot;Alt 2&quot; loading=&quot;lazy&quot;&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;WHY and also, what am I supposed to do with this&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;https://anyadanilova.com/archive/posts/2025-09/img/3.png&quot; alt=&quot;Alt 3&quot; loading=&quot;lazy&quot;&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;Moving points in my script for Black Incised&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;https://anyadanilova.com/archive/posts/2025-09/img/4.png&quot; alt=&quot;Alt 4&quot; loading=&quot;lazy&quot;&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;It may look better than the actual final letters&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
</feed>